Vojislav Zaja

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Passionate about problem solving and creating custom features for a website.

SUMMARY

I have 5 years of experience in Hospitality, but I longed for a change in my life and career. Before I moved to the USA I worked as a Front End Development Intern. Coding has always been my passion and that is the reason I decided to join Ironhack to improve my web development skills. My knowledge of programming languages, business operations, teamwork and flexibility, can help me to achieve and deliver, while always focused on positivity, problem-solving and conflict resolution.

EXPERIENCE

Nobu Eden Roc Hotel, Miami Beach - Bartender / Departmental trainer

December 2016 - May 2021

- Interacted with the hotel guests and ensured they have a great experience.
- Provided job training for new hires.

Monty's Sunset, Miami Beach - Server / Bartender

December 2015 - December 2016

- Maintained dining ambiance with a positive attitude.
- Provided information to help food and beverage selections.

Bit-Soft doo, Serbia – Front End Developer Intern

http://www.bitsoft.rs/

March 2015 - November 2015

- Built different web pages using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Assist in troubleshooting issues on web-based systems.
- Update and edit website content, posts and pages.
- Design, recommend and pitch improvements to new and existing features.
- Assisted in writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices.

Agro-Zavos doo, Serbia - General Manager

September 2012 - February 2015

- · Created and managed budgets.
- Researched and identified growth opportunities.

EDUCATION

Ironhack, Miami - Full Stack Web development (400+hours)

June 2021 - August 2021 - Miami, Fl

High School, Serbia - high school diploma(Electrician)

September 1998 - June 2001

INFO

Miami Beach, FL, United States

E-mail: vojislavzaja@gmail.com

(813) 570 - 3316

LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vojislav-zaja/

GitHub Profile: https://github.com/vojaso82

SKILLS

JavaScript | React.js |
Express.js | MongoDB |
Mongoose | Node.js | HTML |
CSS | Git | GitHub | Heroku |
Cloudinary | REST APIs |
Responsive Web Design

LANGUAGES

English, Serbian

PROJECTS

Reggie Willis - https://ux-portfolio-project.qithub.io/ux-project/index.html

- Designed and created a custom portfolio page as the first project in Ironhack bootcamp.
- TOOLS: HTML, CSS, Git, Figma

Grandmas vs Critters - https://week-4-game-project.github.io/2d-tower-defense/

- A single-player JavaScript based, made with OOP principles.
- TOOLS: JavaScript, Canvas, Git, HTML, CSS

NutriYoga - https://nutriyoga.netlify.app/

- Yoga and nutrition, search for Yoga exercise, find food recipes, meals, plans and add your favorite recipes.
- TOOLS: React, Axios, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Git, YouTube API, Spoonacular API, HTML, CSS

NatureAll - https://natureall.netlify.app/

- A website where you can search for national parks and trails, create your own profile, comment on and like activities.
- TOOLS: Express, Mongoose, Node, Cloudinary, React, Axios, JavaScript, National Parks API, Git, HTML, CSS

ARS paint shop (2015) - https://www.ars.rs/

- Developed a custom online store page which matches the desired design and needed functionality for the client's website.
- TOOLS: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Orthodox Church Switzerland (2015) - https://www.orthodoxchurch.ch/

- Developed orthodox church page which matches the desired design and needed functionality for the client's website.
- TOOLS: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Kita Wolkenland (2015) - http://www.kita-wolkenland.ch/

- Developed a custom home furniture page which matches the desired design and needed functionality for the client's website.
- TOOLS: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Gianni Fröhlich-Bleuler (2015) - https://www.jurpm.ch/en/

- Developed a custom attorney at law page which matches the desired design and needed functionality for the client's website.
- TOOLS: JavaScript, HTML, CSS